[{"answer": "Well, it's just tragic.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "What do you think the movie industry reaction is to this?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes, all that stuff, yes.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "ROFT, 60 MINUTES CORRESPONDENT: So this was drugs or alcohol or both?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "You panic, you panic.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "And why did you decide to stop?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "He was a very private man, you know.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "What was he like as a man, for people who didn't know Philip Seymour Hoffman?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I think actors, I mean he opened up to them actually, as private as he was, he opened up to his peers.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "As an actor, what made him so special?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I've known Woody for a really long time.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What do you think of these claims and charges from Dylan Farrow?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "I'm getting through to you?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "So, there's never anything illegal about it?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Why do you think that Mia Farrow is helping her daughter and she's been backed by her son Ronan and (inaudible), why do you think they're going through all of this if they had simply all invented it?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Oh no, no, no, not at all.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "So, you personally have no issue with what he did?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, it wasn't Mia herself.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "What exactly did she asked you to do?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Well, I recollected very well, I wrote about it, I have a chapter in my book, \"Taking the Stand\" about the case, and I went back and read all the transcripts in order to prepare for writing the books.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What is your recollection at that period because that seems to be the crucial element really of -- everything has blown up again this week?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I had no reason to disbelieve.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "So did you believed her at that time when she told you about the abuse allegations involving Dylan?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Statute limitation is almost certainly expired.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Is it still possible for Woody Allen to face any charges or has statute limitations now expired in this particular kind of case?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, first let me just point about Allan Dershowitz, that he is a lawyer here.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Why do you believe them?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "That's not in dispute, either but the two facts I wanted to put here just ask you your impression really is when -- is there any way of assessing the character of Woody Allen when you take that fact and you take the fact that Allen to be somebody who's now having an affair with when he was 42 and he found this girl, 17, on the set of one of his movies and so you (inaudible) with her?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "When you put them both together, is it inappropriate enough?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "But you're doing this wrong because what you're saying is that this is a man who had -- had a relationship that you might call inappropriate, not illegal and therefore, then this is the leap that you're making here whether you're saying it or not, therefore, it's likely he molested a seven-year old.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "Do you think there is something wrong with (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Michael, I'm in a bizarre -- Michael, I'm in this composition of...", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Have you ever been attracted to an 18-year-old woman?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "... having to jump in an answer a question on my own show.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Have you ever been?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Some would say a lot of...", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "... who knows?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I don't know that you haven't molested someone.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "But what I was saying is because you don't know that it didn't happen either, do you, in the same position as me?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "LOOM: Well, first of all, I've never met anybody in this case.", "docId": "140203pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "What should we make of this?", "qSentId": 543}]